ELISABETH ZAIGER

Full-Stack Developer | Multimedia Artist | Administrative Support

Email: elisabeth.zaiger@gmail.com | Phone: (541) 281-3613 | LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/elisabethzaiger

Summary

Front-end developer with a background in studio and digital art. Trained at the University of Oregon coding bootcamp and earned a certificate in full-stack web development. Innovative problem-solver passionate about developing apps; focused on mobile-first design and development. Strengths in creativity, teamwork, and building projects from ideation to execution.

Technical Skills

Software/Platforms: Microsoft Windows, iOS, Microsoft Office Suite, Adobe Creative Suite Software Languages: JavaScript, HTML, CSS, SQL

Core Competencies

- Multi-tasking
- Travel Arrangements
- Computer Savvy
- Data Entry
- Document Formatting
- Photo Staging
- Print Production

- Oral & Written Communication
- Graphic Design
- Office Functions Support
- Meeting & Event Coordination
- Budget Management
- Photography (Digital & Film)
- Typing Speed of 65 WPM

- Organization
- Customer Service
- Work in Fast-Paced Environments; Tight Deadlines
- Supply Purchasing
- OLCC & Food Handler License
- CPR Certified

EDUCATION

Southern Oregon University | Ashland, OR (cum laude – 3.66 GPA)

BFA in Studio Art (Photography & Digital Art)

Minor: Art History

BS in Emerging Media & Digital Art (Graphic Design & Illustration)

Minor: Film, Television, and Convergent Media

HIGHLIGHTS

Oregon Tech -

Assisted the dental hygiene faculty with the CODA (Commission on Dental Accreditation) accreditation process which included proof-reading, assembling, and producing six volumes of self-study which contained over 3,000 pages. Continually met and exceeded deadline expectations. Provided volunteer photography and graphic design services for multiple departments. Participated on interview panels for new staff and students.

Department of Human Services -

Was a key player in decreasing our document submission error rate to 1% or less. This error rate was one of the lowest in the entire state of Oregon (roughly 20+ branches). Frequently requested to test document submission methods.

Southern Oregon University –

Researched and developed printer ink and paper usage costs to allow the art department to accurately charge for the cost of printing fine art materials when they were previously estimating costs.

Office Depot -

Received employee of the month on numerous occasions. Streamlined the Copy and Print department by organizing supplies in a way that created faster production results.

EXPERIENCE

Office Specialist 2 (2016-2018)

Administrative Program Specialist (2018-Present)

OREGON TECH | Klamath Falls, OR & Salem, OR | 2016-Present

Provided administrative support to 60 students and 20 faculty members across two campus locations. Duties included but are not limited to: course materials for classroom instruction, budget-related activities for the instructional departments, travel arrangements and various department-specific activities that are assigned to and completed by the office manager. In 2018, due to an unexpected vacancy, moved into a position above previous classification to assist the dental hygiene clinic located at the Chemeketa Community College campus in Salem. Took on the role of clinic manager that assists in the daily operations of a dental clinic.

Office Specialist 2

DEPARTMENT OF HUMAN SERVICES | Klamath Falls, OR | 2015-16

Worked as part of a clerical team to help low-income individuals become self-sufficient through health coverage, job preparation, childcare and other support services. Specifically assigned to take meeting notes, process mail, build customer cases, process documents and submit them to an online database, purchase supplies for the office and back-up other clerical staff with front desk reception, transferring calls, and scheduling as needed.

Photography & Digital Print Lab Supervisor

SOUTHERN OREGON UNIVERSITY | Ashland, OR | 2012-15

Trained and supervised over 40 university student lab aides each term as part of a small team while maintaining the photography lab, digital art labs, digital print lab, and photography equipment checkout room.

Copy and Print Depot Specialist

OFFICE DEPOT | Klamath Falls & Medford, OR | 2008-12

Worked as part of a team to coordinate and plan projects with customers and make costeffective recommendations based on the customer's needs. Assisted with record keeping, supply ordering, inventory, and scheduling of projects.

EXCERPT FROM LETTER(S) OF RECOMMENDATION

- "Her ability to see a need and to immediately address the issue, or recommend solutions, made her a very valuable asset to our office."
- Evelyn R. Hobbs, Former Department Chair of Dental Hygiene at the Oregon Institute of Technology (Oregon Tech)
- "...she is a self-starter who can identify a broad vision, organize people and resources to bring a complex conceptual problem to successful completion."
- Donald Kay, Emeritus Professor of Art at Southern Oregon University
- "Elisabeth has excellent communication skills. In addition, she is extremely organized, reliable and computer literate. ...flexible and willing to work on any project that is assigned to her.
- ...always quick to volunteer to assist in other areas of company operations, as well."
- David Williams, Department Manager at Office Depot